brandchannel.com 2009-06-09

# brandchannel.com | disclaimer

  |  About Us |    
  | 

Brandchannel.com launched on February 5, 2001, by Interbrand, as the world’s only online exchange about branding. It has grown to become a valuable resource to a growing database of subscribers and countless other readers. 

Brandchannel.com is committed to providing a global perspective on brands. Challenging viewers to think further about the important issues that are affecting brands now and in the future. To further enhance brand awareness, we offer tools and information including global listings for conferences, courses and careers, as well as links to other valuable industry resources. Brandchannel is not a one-way street; we provide the opportunity for an open exchange on the subject of brands and branding from practitioners around the world through features like online debates, and white paper submissions. Brandchannel.com is unique from other branding-related websites in that it is global in scope, offers original branding content, has an independent, unique voice, is easy to navigate, has no membership fees, and appeals to a wide range of skill levels. 

Brandchannel.com. The world's only online exchange about branding.

|    
  |   |    
  |  Contact Us |    
  | 

**Brandchannel.com**   
130 Fifth Avenue   
New York, NY 10011   
tel: + 1 (212) 798-7597   
fax: + 1 (212) 798-7672 

For general site questions, please email: [question@brandchannel.com](mailto:question@brandchannel.com)

|    
   
  |  Brandchannel Contributors |    
  | 

John Allert, Kim Barnet, Michelle Boisson, A.K.Cabell, Ian Cocoran, Edwin Colyer, Randall Frost, Vincent Grimaldi, Evelyn Hafferty, Ron Irwin, Anil Kachala, Preeti Khicha, Sergey Khorenko, Kartikeya Kompella, Asher J. Levine, Vivian Manning-Schaffel, Pete Markiewicz, Alycia de Mesa, Joe Ray, Robin Rusch, Abram Sauer, Cristi Sauser, Barry Silverstein, Michael Standaert, Jeff Swystun, James Thompson, Tasha Walters, Iris Yee, Anthony Zumpano. 

|    
   
  |  Brandchannel Privacy Policy |    
  |  Brandchannel.com respects your right to the privacy of the personal information you provide us on our website. To that end, unless you designate otherwise or we state otherwise in this policy or at the time information is collected, any personal information you provide to brandchannel.com will be known only to two parties: you and brandchannel.com. The following policy is intended to explain how your personal information will be treated as you make use of our site and its features. Personal information includes your name and e-mail addresses, click-through activity and any other personal information you may provide here. This policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically.  |    
  |  |    
  |  Traffic data

Each time a visitor comes to the brandchannel.com website, our server -- like most on the web -- collects some basic technical information, including, for example, your domain name (e.g., whether the user has logged on from aol.com or whitehouse.gov), referral data (e.g., we record the address of the last URL a user visited prior to clicking through to brandchannel.com) and browser and platform type (e.g., a Netscape browser on a Macintosh platform). 

We also count, track and aggregate the visitor's activity into our analysis of general traffic flows at our site (e.g., tracking where traffic comes from, how traffic flows within the site, etc.). To these ends, we may merge information about visitors and visits into group data; but we will not disclose your individual identity or personally identifiable data without your permission. When we do present aggregated information to outside companies we do so only in the format of anonymous statistics, meaning that no one will ever be able to identify you or contact you. 

|    
  |   |    
  | 

Email alert feature

After signing up to receive an e-mail alert, users will start receiving an email delivered on a regular basis as new issues of the brandchannel are posted. We collect subscribers' e-mail addresses in order to distribute those newsletters and announcements and do not otherwise share them with any other companies or partners. Users can choose to unsubscribe from brandchannel.com newsletters at any time by following the unsubscribe instructions found in each e-mail. To register for e-mail alerts, click here. 

|    
  |   |    
  |  Article and Brand Debate Comments 

Each commenter is asked to provide us with his or her full name, job title, affiliated organization and working email address. We do not sell or redistribute your personal information and will not send email to the provided address, except in rare cases to reply to or clarify your comment. Name and affiliation (but not email address) will be posted along with the comment, unless otherwise requested (in which case the comment will appear from anonymous). Participants are expected to comply with the rules governing the comment sections. We cannot, however, control how third parties use information that commenters choose to provide in such a public forum. 

|    
  |   |    
  |  Brand Papers 

Brandchannel.com is not responsible for editing or proofing any of the papers posted on the site. Any inaccuracies or mistakes are those of the author(s). Materials submitted with excessive grammatical or spelling errors will not be considered for posting. The views and opinions on the Papers section are not necessarily those of brandchannel.com or its staff. 

|    
  |   |    
  |  Surveys 

Brandchannel.com will from time to time conduct voluntary surveys of visitors to the site to obtain readers' opinions. Such information may be compiled and shared in the aggregate with the press and other third parties, but no personal details will be traceable or associated with specific individuals. 

|    
  |   |    
  |  Other disclosure of personal information 

Brandchannel.com will not otherwise use or disclose your personal information without your consent except (i) as described in this privacy policy, or (ii) as required by law, court order or as requested by other government or law enforcement authority (i.e., Against our will). 

|    
  |   |    
  | 

Unsubscribe and data removal policies

If you would like to unsubscribe from a brandchannel.com email list, please follow the instructions at the bottom of the email itself. If you would like to remove your name and e-mail address from our Brand Debate database, you can send an e-mail requesting removal to [webmaster@brandchannel.com](mailto:webmaster@brandchannel.com). 

|    
  |   |    
  | 

Other sites 

Brandchannel.com contains many links to other sites on the web. As these sites are not brandchannel partner sites we cannot control and are not responsible for their privacy practices or content. 

|    
  |   |    
  | 

Who can I ask if I have any additional questions? 

If you have any further questions or concerns about our privacy policies and use of personal information, please email [question@brandchannel.com](mailto:question@brandchannel.com). If you have additional questions about brandchannel, check out our [FAQ](http://www.brandchannel.com/faq.asp). 

|    
  |   |    
  |  Brandchannel Terms |    
  | 

This website is copyrighted by Brandchannel.com, all rights reserved. 

The views and opinions expressed on brandchannel.com are not necessarily those of its parent company, Interbrand, or Omnicom or any of its member companies 

Certain material contained on this website may be licensed from third parties, and any copyrights, trademarks or service marks in such content belong to the respective third parties. 

This website and its content, whether statement, expression of opinion or any other matter herein, are not an offer to sell or a solicitation of an offer to buy any security, nor shall any such security be offered or sold to any person, in any jurisdiction in which such offer, solicitation, purchase, or sale may not lawfully be made. 

Please note that Brandchannel.com does not sign non-disclosure agreements and that business information shared in any form with the firm, its employees, and affiliates cannot be considered confidential. 

The information contained in this site is taken from sources believed to be reliable, but its accuracy cannot be guaranteed. 

Brandchannel.com, its principals, employees, and affiliates may at any time hold positions and options in companies discussed herein, and may provide consulting and other services to those companies. 

Brandchannel.com reserves the right to change its terms and policy at any time without prior notice. 

|    
  
Copyright © 2001-2009 brandchannel. All rights reserved.
